<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sports Business on </title>
    <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//tags/sports-business/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sports Business on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <atom:link href="http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//tags/sports-business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Football Director</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//football-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 05:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//football-director/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/directoroffootball_1345180990.gif&#34; style=&#34;float:left;margin-right:5px;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commodity trading or should I say people trading? Think you have an eye for smart investments searching for clues on football player&amp;#8217;s traits that might lead them to global superstars? Try Football Director, starting with 6 players you can exercise your trading expertise right away letting go the 3 worst players.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like the real estate business game you&amp;#8217;ll have players popping up with their prices growing and decreasing quite fast so be cautious to get the best deals, from here you have a football field where the season will be played and you&amp;#8217;re expected to replace the players with the better ones you bough or rotate them to keep&amp;#8217;em fitness.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football Tycoon</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//football-tycoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 21:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//football-tycoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;float: left; margin-right: 5px;&#34; src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/footballtycoon.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Football Tycoon&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think you can manage a soccer team to the heavens and glory? Buying Manchester City straight away would be fun, but you barely have enough millions for a 2nd division team. Will that stop you from finding fortune? Football Tycoon only has 2 teams available to your budget, but millions more are available for a loan. Be prudent, many global reputed teams have huge debts pilling up you wouldn&amp;#8217;t risk loosing Ronaldo if Real Madrid were to miss any payment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And from here begin winning matches and at last the league, at this point, or maybe the year right after you&amp;#8217;ll be able to afford a new team, from the 1st division. This might be easier for you to compete there but you can also try with your current team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within the team management you can upgrade your stadium, control the ticket prices, buy star players, hire the staff, control your´s and club´s debt, corrupt the officials, dope your players and many others things! Are you feeling ready?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>