<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tycoon on </title>
    <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//tags/tycoon/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tycoon on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <atom:link href="http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//tags/tycoon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock Band Simulator</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//rock-band-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 05:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//rock-band-simulator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;float: left; margin-right: 5px;&#34; src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/rockbandsim_1345179711.gif&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;Ever dreamed being a rock star? Rock Band Sim gives you the possibility of taking a look over it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From accepting penny-rewarding gigs to get the initial hype and money for the first recordings to the biggest arenas of the country, wherever real rock stars do, you can do it here!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#8217;ll also have a guitar-hero kind of mini-game for the gigs and recordings, it might become a bit boring after a whole hour playing the game, but I will leave it for you to decide! Begin by taking the smaller gigs and writing some songs and as soon as you have a couple of 4 star musics think about recording them. You might prefer the 800 dollar studio for each of the musics so you don&amp;#8217;t loose it&amp;#8217;s rating from the recording process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you keep playing begin buying new instruments for your players, this will give a fast increase of skills for the band&amp;#8217;s members and improve the results of recordings and gigs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have available PR campaigns as well, use them after releasing a new album as your budget allows it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And take care not to waste all of your money, if you&amp;#8217;re not selling albums or singles so that you don&amp;#8217;t have to do the small venues gigs to have enough money to return for the bigger ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by taking the smaller gigs and writing some songs and as soon as you have a couple of 4 star musics think about recording them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might prefer the 800 dollar studio for each of the musics so you don&amp;#8217;t loose it&amp;#8217;s rating from the recording process. As you keep playing begin buying new instruments for your players, this will give a fast increase of skills for the band&amp;#8217;s members and improve the results of recordings and gigs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have available PR campaigns as well, use them after releasing a new album as your budget allows it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And take care not to waste all of your money, if you&amp;#8217;re not selling albums or singles so that you don&amp;#8217;t have to do the small venues gigs to have enough money to return for the bigger ones.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>