<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strategy Business Games on </title>
    <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//categories/strategy-business-games/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Strategy Business Games on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <atom:link href="http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//categories/strategy-business-games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Merchant Banker</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//merchant-banker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 16:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//merchant-banker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;float: left; margin-right: 5px;&#34; src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/merchantbanker_1345221585.gif&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;How good are your skills as a commodity trader? Try this game where you&amp;#8217;ll to see how much can you make for your pension, at the age of 30. Live the American Dream!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides the trading you have the possibility as well of buying fancy clothes, cars and millionaire real estate. That way you can meet beautiful women and find better jobs on the bar or private clubs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football Director</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//football-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 05:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//football-director/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/directoroffootball_1345180990.gif&#34; style=&#34;float:left;margin-right:5px;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commodity trading or should I say people trading? Think you have an eye for smart investments searching for clues on football player&amp;#8217;s traits that might lead them to global superstars? Try Football Director, starting with 6 players you can exercise your trading expertise right away letting go the 3 worst players.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like the real estate business game you&amp;#8217;ll have players popping up with their prices growing and decreasing quite fast so be cautious to get the best deals, from here you have a football field where the season will be played and you&amp;#8217;re expected to replace the players with the better ones you bough or rotate them to keep&amp;#8217;em fitness.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock Band Simulator</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//rock-band-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 05:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//rock-band-simulator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;float: left; margin-right: 5px;&#34; src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/rockbandsim_1345179711.gif&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;Ever dreamed being a rock star? Rock Band Sim gives you the possibility of taking a look over it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From accepting penny-rewarding gigs to get the initial hype and money for the first recordings to the biggest arenas of the country, wherever real rock stars do, you can do it here!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#8217;ll also have a guitar-hero kind of mini-game for the gigs and recordings, it might become a bit boring after a whole hour playing the game, but I will leave it for you to decide! Begin by taking the smaller gigs and writing some songs and as soon as you have a couple of 4 star musics think about recording them. You might prefer the 800 dollar studio for each of the musics so you don&amp;#8217;t loose it&amp;#8217;s rating from the recording process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you keep playing begin buying new instruments for your players, this will give a fast increase of skills for the band&amp;#8217;s members and improve the results of recordings and gigs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have available PR campaigns as well, use them after releasing a new album as your budget allows it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And take care not to waste all of your money, if you&amp;#8217;re not selling albums or singles so that you don&amp;#8217;t have to do the small venues gigs to have enough money to return for the bigger ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by taking the smaller gigs and writing some songs and as soon as you have a couple of 4 star musics think about recording them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might prefer the 800 dollar studio for each of the musics so you don&amp;#8217;t loose it&amp;#8217;s rating from the recording process. As you keep playing begin buying new instruments for your players, this will give a fast increase of skills for the band&amp;#8217;s members and improve the results of recordings and gigs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have available PR campaigns as well, use them after releasing a new album as your budget allows it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And take care not to waste all of your money, if you&amp;#8217;re not selling albums or singles so that you don&amp;#8217;t have to do the small venues gigs to have enough money to return for the bigger ones.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diner City</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//diner-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 22:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//diner-city/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;float: left; margin-right: 5px;&#34; src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/13567.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;Run your own restaurant and beat your opponent! After choosing and buying the land where you´re going to build your restaurant you´re given the possibility of improving the serving speed with new employees and adding upgrades for better profit or increased capacity. Beat your opponent reaching first to the target goal.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Tycoon</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//real-estate-tycoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 21:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//real-estate-tycoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;float: left; margin-right: 5px;&#34; src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/Real_Estate_Tycoon_180.gif&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;Become the real estate mogul in this simulation game. The goal? Make profit buying low and selling high so you can buy the house of your dreams!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopping Street</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//shopping-street/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 17:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//shopping-street/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/7195.png&#34; style=&#34;float:left;margin-right:5px;&#34; /&gt;Can you build your strip mall empire? Build and upgrade shops along the street, slow down your potential costumers adding benches, news-stand and music ads; bring more costumers adding a Bus Stop and let the time flow (and the money, of course)!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporation Inc.</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//corporation-inc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 17:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//corporation-inc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/7367.png&#34; style=&#34;float:left;margin-right:5px;&#34; /&gt;Build your corporate empire with your own self sky-rise offices! Build new offices, hire workers, supervisors, janitors, it techs and researchers for later upgrades on your office and staff. Make your staff´s life the Heaven or Hell, you choose!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oiligarchy</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//oiligarchy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 18:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//oiligarchy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/oiligarchy_pic_1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Oiligarchy&#34; style=&#34;float:left;margin-right:5px;&#34; /&gt;Ever heard about the Rockafeller petro fortune of half a trillion dollars? From a small backyard drilling operation in Texas to a global corporation of evil and greed. In this game you´ll have to explore and drill some of the richest zones in the planet in a matter of crude oil, corrupt the politicians and with them, control the world. For a never ending stream of profits, Oiligarchy is the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WindFall Tycoon</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//windfall-tycoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 17:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//windfall-tycoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/5996.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;WindFall Tycoon&#34; style=&#34;float:left;margin-right:5px;&#34; /&gt;Capitalism isn&amp;#8217;t all about greed, Middle East wars, illegal logging on the amazon rainforest or toxic waste dumping. From a tiny wind mill to the whole supplier of a demanding city energy market, on WindFall Tycoon you can become a Energy mogul, you won&amp;#8217;t have to learn to fly, but taking advantage of the wind energy isn&amp;#8217;t a bad idea either.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football Tycoon</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//football-tycoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 21:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//football-tycoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;float: left; margin-right: 5px;&#34; src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/footballtycoon.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Football Tycoon&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think you can manage a soccer team to the heavens and glory? Buying Manchester City straight away would be fun, but you barely have enough millions for a 2nd division team. Will that stop you from finding fortune? Football Tycoon only has 2 teams available to your budget, but millions more are available for a loan. Be prudent, many global reputed teams have huge debts pilling up you wouldn&amp;#8217;t risk loosing Ronaldo if Real Madrid were to miss any payment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And from here begin winning matches and at last the league, at this point, or maybe the year right after you&amp;#8217;ll be able to afford a new team, from the 1st division. This might be easier for you to compete there but you can also try with your current team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within the team management you can upgrade your stadium, control the ticket prices, buy star players, hire the staff, control your´s and club´s debt, corrupt the officials, dope your players and many others things! Are you feeling ready?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand Prix Tycoon</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//grand-prix-tycoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 20:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//grand-prix-tycoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/Grand_Prix_Tycoon180.gif&#34; style=&#34;float:left;margin-right:5px;&#34; /&gt;Manage your own Formula 1 racing team! After your investor have found 2 million under his sofa, he has decided to invest them on you. Make him pride and build a successful team! For that, you have to hire a driver, a hot grid girl and pit crew, build your race car and race through the whole season of the Grand Prix(GP).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger Tycoon</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//burger-tycoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 20:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//burger-tycoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/Burger_Tycoon180.gif&#34; style=&#34;float:left;margin-right:5px;&#34; /&gt;Run your own fast-food empire! In this game your task is to manage a multinational fast-food company. Your management begins on the land plots, where you will grow livestock (cows) and corn to feed them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The feedlot where your cows are fattened and processed into burgers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The store where you have to manage the staff in order to serve your clients efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The headquarters, where you invest in advertising campaigns and corrupt influential people to keep your costumers/profit coming.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airport Tycoon</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//airport-tycoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 20:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//airport-tycoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/Airport_Tycoon180.gif&#34; style=&#34;float:left;margin-right:5px;&#34; /&gt;Run your own airport! In this game your job is to keep the runways in good conditions (and even build more), investing in better caffes and shops for your costumers, buying new routes for your planes, hiring tv stars to promote your empire and, of course, keep the baggage handling and the passport control department upgraded so it can serve all your daily passengers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Tycoon</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//coffee-tycoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 20:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//coffee-tycoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/Coffee-Tycoon180.gif&#34; style=&#34;float:left;margin-right:5px;&#34; /&gt;Build your own coffee shop empire! In this simulation game, your job is to manage your coffee´s staff depending on your own goals (to achieve game´s goals) of: making money, increase costumers or increase the number of shops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As your business grows you can use the money you earn on improvements for your empire, like buying new recipes for your menu, advertising to bring more costumers, new equipment for increased income and many others options.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RecordShop Tycoon</title>
      <link>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//recordshop-tycoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 19:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//recordshop-tycoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http:https://whogonstopme.github.io/onlinegamestycoon//wp-content/thumbs/13927_small.jpg&#34; style=&#34;float:left;margin-right:5px;&#34; /&gt;Run your own record store in Rubato Hills and become the major store in the city. Some of the tasks you´re assigned to are to do purche the CDs, improve your store with upgrades, invest in advertising, etc. Are you ready for this challenge?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>